renegadeuniversity.com 2013-11-16

# MarketingMerge.com: Privacy Policy

Marketing Merge, Inc. - Network Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Marketing Merge, Inc. and reviewing the Privacy Policy.

We take your privacy seriously and are committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read this policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you take advantage of the information and services available at our Site.

Renegade Professional is licensed by Marketing Merge, Inc. (hereinafter referred to as "We", or "Us"), which operates web sites accessible through www.MarketingMerge.com, among other URLs (collectively referred to as "Marketing Merge, Inc." or "the Site").

**Overview**

This Privacy Policy (hereinafter "Policy") governs your use of the Marketing Merge, Inc. websites. The Policy describes the information we collect from you and how we may use it to better serve you. 

This Policy will let you know what information we collect from you; what cookies are used and how they are used; how your information is utilized; who is collecting your information; with whom your information may be shared; what options are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information; how you may use other users' information ("Users"); the types of security precautions in place to protect against loss, misuse, or alteration of your information; how Marketing Merge, Inc. protects children's privacy; and other details you may want to know about your privacy online. 

Please note that our privacy practices are subject to change from time to time. Please visit this page periodically to ensure you follow the most current version of this Policy. All amended terms shall be effective after being posted at the Site. 

By visiting the Site, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, please do not use or access the Site. 

**What Personally Identifiable Information does Marketing Merge, Inc. collect?**

The primary purpose of collecting information from you is to provide you with a safe, smooth, effective, and personalized experience and to fulfill the transactions you undertake here. We only collect information about you that we consider necessary to achieve these purposes. 

Generally, we collect information in two ways. Some information is gathered when you access free areas within our secured Site. This may include your name, email address, address, and phone number. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. We may also collect personal information when you contact us with questions or feedback. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence to better serve you going forward. 

Wherever Marketing Merge, Inc. collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

**What are "cookies" and how does Marketing Merge, Inc. use them?**

Data collection devices, such as "cookies," are used to store, and sometimes track, information about you. Generally, these cookies help provide personalized services and promote trust and safety. A cookie is a small file containing a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and placed on your computer's hard drive to assist us in providing our services. All pages on the Site where you are prompted to login or that are customizable request that you accept cookies. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them and are unable to execute any code or virus. Most cookies are "session cookies," and are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. 

More specifically, we use cookies to remind us of who you are and to access your account information in order to deliver to you a more personalized service. We also use cookies, along with IP addresses, to measure your visiting patterns in the aggregate. We use this research to understand how our users' habits are similar or different from one another so that we can make each new experience on the Marketing Merge, Inc. Sites a better one. We may also use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you and other Users will see on our Site. 

**How does the Marketing Merge, Inc. use my information?**

We use your information to provide you with a customized website experience. We also may use your personal information to manage and monitor your purchases with us; communicate with you; resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; manage and operate our marketing programs; detect and protect against error, fraud, or other criminal activity; and enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement. 

**Who is collecting information?**

When you are using the Site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with the Marketing Merge, Inc. and, if you arrived at the Site via an affiliate link or affiliate of the Marketing Merge, Inc., then with that affiliate as well. 

Please be advised that the Marketing Merge, Inc. affiliates, advertisers, and Web sites that have links on our Site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those affiliates, advertisers, and Web sites linked to the Marketing Merge, Inc. are not covered by this privacy statement. 

**With whom does the Marketing Merge, Inc. share my information?**

Generally, we will not disclose your personally identifiable information unless we have your permission or under certain circumstances, such as those described below. 

_Affiliates:_

If you have visited the Marketing Merge, Inc. website through a link provided by an affiliate of Marketing Merge, Inc. ("Affiliate"), we will share your personally identifiable information with the Affiliate responsible for your visit and the Affiliate may contact you. 

_Employees, Associates and Consultants:_

To help deliver Marketing Merge, Inc. services and information, we may provide your personally identifiable information to our employees, associates and consultants. All of our employees, associates and consultants are subject to non-disclosure agreements with us. This prohibits their use of the information you provide us for any purpose except to facilitate the operation and activities of the Marketing Merge, Inc., unless you agreed or gave your prior permission to them for additional uses. 

_Third Party Data & Data in the Aggregate:_

Aggregate data (data gathered across all user accounts) may be gathered in a non-personally identifiable form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas and services of the Site. Aggregate data may be disclosed in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, no personal information that could be used to identify you personally is disclosed in these situations. 

_External Service Providers:_

Separate services are offered by third parties, also known as external service providers, some of whom advertise on the Site or are linked to from the Site. If you choose to use these services, disclose information to these parties, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you; their privacy policy governs the use of your information. We will not disclose your personal information to external service providers without your express consent. 

_Business Transaction:_

The Marketing Merge, Inc. reserves the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from visitors, or that we otherwise collect concerning or in connection with the Site, to a third party in the event of a sale or other transfer of assets or of any portion of our business. In the event Marketing Merge, Inc. enters a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information may be among the assets transferred. 

_Other:_

We may disclose account information where we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our services. 

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or Users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. We use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, however, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

**How may I use other users' information?**

Recognizing the global nature of the Internet, you agree to comply with all applicable local laws and rules regarding online conduct and privacy, as well as content. Specifically, but not as a limitation, you agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding transmission of technical and personal data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside. 

**What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?**

Whenever the Marketing Merge, Inc. handles your personal information, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement and this Policy. We use procedural and mechanical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including encryption. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot, therefore, warrant or ensure the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

**How are children's privacy protected?**

Children under the age of 18 are not authorized to use the Site and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. 

**Additional Information**

Any questions regarding this statement should be directed to: [support@marketingmerge.com](emailto:support@marketingmerge.com)

This Policy is the sole authorized statement of the Marketing Merge, Inc.’s practices with respect to the online collection of personally identifiable information and the usage of such information. Any summaries of this Policy generated by third party software or otherwise shall have no legal effect, are in no way binding upon the Marketing Merge, Inc., shall not be relied upon in substitute for this Policy, and neither supersede nor modify this Policy.
